---------------------------------------------------------------
1  I am f1 file  
2  Success is a journey not a destination 
3   
4  Never say never 
5   
6  Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. 
7   
8  Success is how high you bounce when you hit bottom. 
9   
10  Success is the progressive realization of predetermined, worthwhile, personal goals. 
11   
12  When it comes to success, there are no shortcuts. 
13   
14  Success is not in what you have, but who you are. 
15   
16  Love yourself first and everything else falls into line. You really have to love yourself to get anything done in this world. 
17   
18  If you want to live a happy life, tie it to a goal, not to people or things. 
19  I am f2 file 
20  never says never 
21   
22  Positive anything is better than negative nothing. 
23   
24  One small positive thought can change your whole day. 
25   
26  Be positive. Be true. Be kind. 
27   
28  You cannot have a positive life and a negative mind. 
29   
30  If you are positive, youΓÇÖll see opportunities instead of obstacles. 
31   
32  Write it on your heart that every day is the best day in the year. 
33   
34  Accentuate the positive, Eliminate the Negative, latch onto the affirmative. 
35   
36  A positive atmosphere nurtures a positive attitude, which is required to take positive action. 
37   
